Inventions are the handwork of mortal man.
Though at first they appeal to us as something normal
we ought to look at them as wonderful creations of human ingenuity.
Their ultimate fate is to become more or less commonplace.
The telegraph, and telephone, dynamo and motor,
the light of the electrical arc and of the incandescent filament,
had lost much of their awe - inspiring character
even at the time when I was a student at Cambridge.
Inventions age and are superseded by other inventions and
being the creation of the constructive schemes of a mortal man, are themselves mortal.
But the laws which the stars and the planets obey and have always obeyed
in their paths through the heavens are unchangeable;
They never age, and therefore they are immortal;
they are a part of the the eternal truth.
We do not know of any natural processes by which eternal things have been evolved.
Their existence is the best philosophic proof that back of all this changeable visible world
there is the unchangeable, the eternal divinity.